<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.pedropaulo.OzemPDF</id>
  <name>OzemPDF</name>
  <summary>Compacte arquivos PDF com presets praticos e em lote</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en">Compress PDF files with practical presets and batch tools</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Comprime archivos PDF con ajustes practicos y en lote</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Compressez des PDF avec des reglages pratiques et en lot</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">PDF-Dateien mit praktischen Vorgaben und Stapelverarbeitung komprimieren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Comprimi PDF con preset pratici e strumenti batch</summary>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <developer id="net.pedropaulo">
    <name>Pedro Paulo</name>
  </developer>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.pedropaulo.OzemPDF.desktop</launchable>
  <description>
    <p>OzemPDF e um aplicativo desktop para comprimir um ou varios arquivos PDF com presets praticos, dialogos nativos e fluxo em lote.</p>
    <p>O projeto e distribuido sob a licenca MIT.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">OzemPDF is a desktop app for compressing one or many PDF files with practical presets, native file dialogs, and a straightforward batch workflow.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">The project is distributed under the MIT license.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">OzemPDF es una aplicacion de escritorio para comprimir uno o varios archivos PDF con ajustes practicos, dialogos nativos y un flujo por lotes sencillo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El proyecto se distribuye bajo la licencia MIT.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">OzemPDF est une application de bureau pour compresser un ou plusieurs fichiers PDF avec des reglages pratiques, des dialogues natifs et un traitement par lot simple.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le projet est distribue sous licence MIT.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">OzemPDF ist eine Desktop-Anwendung zum Komprimieren einer oder mehrerer PDF-Dateien mit praktischen Vorgaben, nativen Dateidialogen und einem unkomplizierten Stapelablauf.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Projekt wird unter der MIT-Lizenz veroeffentlicht.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">OzemPDF e un'app desktop per comprimere uno o piu file PDF con preset pratici, finestre di dialogo native e un flusso batch lineare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il progetto e distribuito con licenza MIT.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://dev.pedropaulo.net/ozempdf</url>
  <url type="donation">https://ko-fi.com/pedropaulo</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Fluxo de compactacao em lote no OzemPDF</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en">Batch compression workflow in OzemPDF</caption>
      <image>https://dev.pedropaulo.net/ozempdf/assets/Screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>ozempdf</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="0.1.0-beta.2" date="2026-03-22" />
  </releases>
</component>
